Love. Joy. Struggle. Strength. Love.
Bears is a documentary film directed by Keith Scholey.
Filmmakers Alastair Fothergill and Keith Scholey chronicle a year in the lives of
an Alaskan brown bear named Sky and her cubs, Scout and Amber.
Their saga begins as the bears emerge from hibernation at the end of winter.
As time passes, the bear family must work together to find food and
stay safe from other predators, especially other bears.
Although their world is exciting, it is also risky, and the
cubs' survival hinges on family togetherness.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by John C. Reilly.
Bears is a 2014 American nature documentary film about a family of brown
bears living in the coastal mountain ranges of Alaska.
Directed by Alastair Fothergill and Keith Scholey and narrated by John C.
Reilly, Bears was released theatrically by Disneynature on April 18, 2014,
the seventh nature documentary released under that label.
It generally received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of symbolism, grizzly
bear, symbol, alaska, wild animal.